- remove win console arg to not scare people.
- Update yaml to support better macOS execution chances.
- Update to build.gradle and yaml to attempt to get the macOS build working.
- Ball cleanup - removed new random() instantiation, using leveldata seed now, which should halp with deterministic ball behaviour (particularly relating to foliage)
- leveldatagenerator cleanup. More cleanups to follow prior to database/highscore setup, also using map seed for foliage collisions.
- Fixed bug around map generation - standard play is no longer fixed to a seed of -1 (bush world)
- fixed 18-hole android menu buttons etc.
- Set up 18-hole persistence, cleanup and extraction of a few helper classes with the main game loop. Next up is to ensure we can't replay the 18 holes.
- Fixed both plausible user exploits around resets to get away with bad shots/holes
- Saving progress within holes now - have noted a couple of bugs to be fixed first though.
- Fix to difficulty menu selection - can now go back
- Added new difficulty tiers and locking with the use of GameSession, which will also track everything required for saving and restoring sessions later
- Added daily 18 mode, and better nested menu options. Added new difficulty tiers
- Updated crater fields to have slightly more random craters with a larger, flatter rock in the centre to act as a potential target added simplex niose util
- updated levelfactory to make the driving range longer - required for the new terrain and club stats.
- Updated club interactions, and tested. Updated club info to reflect - looks like it's pretty much consistent now. Pushing before further playtest. As it stands, this is a 1.2.0 release candidate.
- More terrain and interaction tweaks - things looking pretty good now. Just need to udpate the club spin implementation - lob wedges currently applying wayyy too much spin.
- Started tweaking physics, ended up making a couple of small practice range tweaks and fixes also. Main physics tweak yet to come.
- Minor map tweaks, got rid of penalty stroke (was incorrect given golf rules)
- Added cliperton map
- Added bunkers, 3 random types. All tested and looks good on Desktop.
- Tons more mobile tweaks and fixes, as well as reverting some desktop stuff (spindicator) that was broken by mobile.
- Fixed fonts on mobile. Also some minor mapo tweaking. Pushing before attempting to create android releasable
- full repo code format and import cleanup
- Fixed instructions page, updated shouts to appear in nicer places on the screen and with a title/subtitle format.
- fixed sidebars and windicator
- Raised power bar size and flag scaling on android.
- didn't apply water depth pass, but applied another fix that probably works better. Will consider upadting all maps to "steepen" water entries though.
- visual water/land bug is prety much fixed - pushing before applying a "water depth pass" to improve it a bit.
- add near-instant OB call on Water contact/OB bounce when OB, maintained grace period on IB water contact.
- re-added shouts
- Added next level button on mobile
- Added shot cancellation, and updated spindicator quit-out to not apply there.
- Plumbed in overhead and shot distance complete with refactors around controls
- Moved the club+_ buttons down to bottom left and replaced them with un-plumbed distance and overview buttons. Rewrote club title info stream, UI behaviour unchanged. Next si to
- More updates to freezing the aim during various minigame phases - complete for desktop, needs verification on controller.
- Updated spin/direction shot for desktop, seems to be working ok. Now to attempt for android
- Add big spindicator for android
- Add max power button
- Updated club info box to show only stats on android interface, no paragraph.
- typo fix
- More HUD text moved around and rescaled on android. Seems perfectly fine at this point.
- windicator scaled up and shifted over to make way for range finder.
- Moved/scaled up a bunch of buttons - WIP.
- fixed drag/pan on mobile
- phase 4 complete, onto bug fixes next.
- Moved some code around and extracted more from HUD.
- Extracted out another class, fixed windicator issue.
- HUD class cleanup/extraction phase 2 complete. extracted out ui utils, notifications (somewhat), mod animation, hold button.
- HUD class cleanup/extraction phase 1 complete.
- Progress made, however a lot of large, ugly classes and regression issues. Junie broke, so doing manual debugging and updates before using a better LLM assistant for new feature help
- Huge code refactor and cleanup. Also added tests.
- pushing something that wasn't pushed with previous for some reason
- Got application running on test android device. Nest up - huge code cleanup refactor to begin to prepare the way for desktop-android split.
- HUGE shift that will begin to enable android development. All functionality shifted to within Core, and so far appears to be working - not expected that any functionality will break as a result.
- Some profiling and map tweaks to try and chase those frames that are dropping - no luck so far. Pushing before a dramatic attempt to start looking at android.
